This bumper is here, it's cut here
Shaheen's friend has thought of getting it done
at a service station, so
he's also paid 1000 from out of country, and the
payment has been made, this is
on Android WhatsApp,
so what about the rear bumper in the car,
Amarnath, two-three days ago, I'll tell you, there was a
cut in our rear bumper, if you see, in
fact, wait,
this is the bumper behind here,
it's cut here,
I have to get it repaired, right now the police are
looking into it, how do I do it, click on it, so this
bumper, which I told you is cut from the back, so
here we have appointed it in the insurance, the
charges on taking insurance will be like this,
subscribe there
and
subscribe, on
Friday I'll
play the song, I'll show you the song, which is the
engine start song from Carrier,
okay, so look brother, this is that
song
[music]
that this
mansion is going to be fun, I feel like
how will you tell me in the center, they are not able to understand
that someone has come inside to get their work fixed  It is
not even there, how can you tell them
that I will take the car to Papa, so
here I keep
typing, we are about to
reach here,
here I have said one and a half Muzaffar, it is not possible,
then my
Piswai brother
glue that
every
service, service, service, service, what does that mean, that happened, the
MP3, the
robber was caught on
Thursday, we will take it, hey, while doing this,
my
tablet is stuck, where is the
Jai Hind
sign, move aside, I
am organizing your inspection, should I give
you the net, do it,
where are you, they will
take another one, it is going on right now, so we
[music] have to
talk about the insurance here,
if you give me the insurance papers, we will talk about it,
okay, let's
touch the feet of
this peon in
wheat, let's
start the car,
so let's check this uncle's operation, this
car has broken down, has the car broken down,
now this, this, this, this, this, when the car
starts, we will check his
invalids, how will the question be, there is more, the
car came Edison, I don't know what
he did in the car, so we did a sting operation
in the car,
look at this, speeding, then
check your urine  It's
difficult to live new and this is absolutely the
recent one that you have ruined so
far,
now it will cost money, anyway we will take it
now we have
started the car has been damaged form hello hello do that
egg driver then
what should I say that you
are there and
that I have also got it made by staying hungry you are
so busy you have to put all the things
inside the carry bag okay from the car
it is not like that let's put all the
things in the tag
okay you have to put that thing okay yes everything whatever you think is
ours
yes this is also there
put a booklet also
look at the background of this your
sting despite this there is something firm that
why is it not amazing stop it now
MP3 gaan
thumbs up
[Music]
Jhalawar city peer
waqt that
in this film all these
things were taken this
Jhal Dhund
[Music]
Jhal
this problem yes-yes a
look on 5th it has happened
for the complaint by A
that Dubai finally all your insurance work is done
here submit the documents etc
and Navya goes back to home  You are going to drop it here,
after dropping it we will come back tomorrow or day after tomorrow it will take at
least three days, let me get the
car back, there is body
shop work and if we change the bumper there will be a
lot of work, there are charges for the car, so let you know
how he will
come to take delivery, I will
tell you how he will do it, right now he has to
run upwards from there,
now for half the fuel,
fast something, he had asked for it to be
so expensive, so
I told him that I will drop it right now
and there is pizza bread here,
I will get you whatever pizza you need,
okay and let me show
you how it was done, there is a
machine inside here, we will do it with you, okay, you have to
tighten it to start
or like this, give
Gautam Buddha 102 from there, we will do it,
hmm, okay, Zeeshan will pick the
north-east corner, we have to prove, pick that one, is
this non-veg or non-veg
Chicken is there you can do vaginal message check
correct Surya click on activate this is
now in front of the force okay now which chili do
you like see which thing
you like this is also below check
share check this thing which one
against nine impress this this this capsicum olive oil
black lips and capsicum Android Africa
Russia
that no's primary can
you Samsung and ho or festival loot move move
view cart answer view
cart or grade interview cut that record
also you will get extra you if you want to take benefits choco
lava cake then you can take this
from here garlic bread bread bread is next next anything is
not
supported Yashwant placeholder spoon order
and email leaders optional and continue and
payment voucher payment let me to the
payment with ok your payment is done thanks
and this gyan punj loaded yes
[music]
MP3
that
saying this Devta no
[music]
dheer
va
[music]
lightning
fell on two
sides where is the country pizza  I had to make it
here, now if you are wondering how pizza is made,
tell me how to
make a base, son, let's make it, let's see friends, let's
put the base and then
put that cheese inside the pizza base, similarly find
the cheese and this is the cheese we are going to make, hello, the
embryo's name is Arun, son, say this loudly, ah, let's
see how both of these are made, right?
[Music] doing some research on taking delivery, welcome back to take home delivery and now let's enjoy pizza, okay, yes, let's do it, [Music] he said, [Music] then
in the poem, why did you cry,
voicemail my face, Zeeshan,
say something,
where are you going, I have gone
chicken, goodbye, I will put it in the style
I am
very good boy, ah, god
threat,
[Music]
so the
sound changes in the, is there
any
problem,
ah, here is
life, ah, ah, a
great person,
sweet ghee, so let's
not use that,
I have my face,
so finally today I have taken the delivery eggs and the cart, and
I have come with the cart,
and I will tell you  Let me tell you that we have received a
bill of 26 around 20000
in which both the front and back have been changed and
along with this they have
subscribed to my channel
and how these
subscriptions were
subscribed,
now I will tell you so
see this,
if you get your vehicle repaired then
it is a coupon of Tow Correct Bandhan, Bishop
Bandar how do you get some benefits, what is there here is that
if you go to buy insurance then
nowadays there is a scheme for pass,
so at the time of insurance you
can tell them that my life
insurance and machine friend are the same, I
mean last time also I saw it, it was
almost the same on the internet, there was not much
difference in my insurance, so
I thought that let's take it from inside,
friends watching open together in
which I got its Tiwari and now
these two meanings were found, after 24
I was not working in it, that was finally going to end, well
finally now I have
used this above because just now the wait was going to
end but that back  It felt
like it hit the bumper, then after it hit me I was
feeling good inside the car, so I have
already used it and I want to get more claims,
play the role of the car, so I
took cream for both the front bumper and the rear bumper and along with that
I said that it
also depends that something or the other is kept here as well,
so you try to get the claim for both the front and the rear, then
after that
his Saptami in Delhi almost sometimes
called Hira and ₹2 in which both the front and
rear bumpers of mine slept and it has also been donated, so
poverty has not happened,
show your strength of the car, still
on this topic I am
subscribed 562
[music]
so see you guys, now the car is
absolutely new, the car, so the bumper
etc. everything is absolutely new, right now there is
nothing inside the car, so let's see
how much it remains, we will try
that such a train which is bought in the beginning, then you
can say that no car, oh absolutely one, still a little bit or the other happens
and finally again the car of you friends,
so try  If you
go for insurance then check these forensic birthdays from the pass, in
which Akhilesh cream is available,
middlemen coupons are available, so hopefully if you
get them then its flavour will be 100,
which are franchisee, then you will get
notepad two watching and this will also be
topper, so it is very good, I have made this cream,
let's meet again
with the next video, till then goodbye, it's a
rural
problem.